[
  {
    "Number": 1,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 2,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 40 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 3,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 45 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 150,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 4,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 105 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 7200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 5,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 700 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 420,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 6,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 80 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2700 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 7,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 135 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 6300 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 8,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 90 mg <br>Substance D: 120 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 6400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 560,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 9,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 45 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 700 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 210,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 10,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 10 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 145 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 3000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 725,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 11,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 20 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 80 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 3600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 12,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 45 mg <br>Substance D: 100 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 13,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 2500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 475,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 14,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 85 mg <br>Substance D: 150 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 750,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 15,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 45 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 4800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 16,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 100 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 17,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 245,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 18,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 480,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 19,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 180 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 7200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 20,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 85 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 110,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 21,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 45 mg <br>Substance D: 30 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 1800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 630,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 22,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 45 mg <br>Substance B: 90 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 60,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 23,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 40 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 24,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 100 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 40 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 2000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 500,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 25,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 85 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 100 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 150,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 26,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 10 mg <br>Substance D: 65 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 900 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 27,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 100 mg <br>Substance C: 90 mg <br>Substance D: 75 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 28,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 640,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 29,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 80 mg <br>Substance B: 90 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 140 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 30,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 31,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 30 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 475,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 32,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 20 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 80 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 3000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 33,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 900 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 210,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 34,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 100 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 2400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 35,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 90 mg <br>Substance C: 10 mg <br>Substance D: 115 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 920,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 36,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 100 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 280,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 37,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 85 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 4000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 760,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 38,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 20 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 85 mg <br>Substance D: 95 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 3600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 630,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 39,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 110 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 660,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 40,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 80 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 320,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 41,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 6300 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 585,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 42,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 105 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 1800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 150,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 43,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 85 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 70 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 4200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 510,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 44,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 45,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 45 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 100 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 900,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 46,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 30 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 47,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 48,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 135 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 6300 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 495,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 49,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 20 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 115 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 50,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 90 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 85 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 2100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 51,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 45 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 3000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 330,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 52,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 85 mg <br>Substance D: 30 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 210,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 53,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 420,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 54,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 45 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 135,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 55,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 100 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 56,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 57,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 25 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 85 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 425,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 58,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 95 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 5400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 390,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 59,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 90 mg <br>Substance D: 90 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 6300 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 810,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 60,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 700 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 61,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 62,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 85 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 5400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 315,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 63,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 3000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 64,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 85 mg <br>Substance D: 55 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 6400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 65,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 66,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 145 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 3500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 67,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 120 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 150,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 68,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 80 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 55 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 480,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 69,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 125 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 4500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 70,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 25 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 155 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 4900 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 350,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 71,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 65 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 385,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 72,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 165 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 5400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 570,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 73,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 85 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 315,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 74,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 95 mg <br>Substance C: 90 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2700 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 285,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 75,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 110 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 4500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 270,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 76,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 40 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 77,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 78,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 130,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 79,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 80 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4900 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 560,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 80,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 85 mg <br>Substance B: 100 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 170,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 81,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 82,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 85 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 200 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 195,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 83,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 84,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 40 mg <br>Substance D: 55 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 4000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 550,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 85,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 55 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 7200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 585,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 86,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 70 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 1000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 87,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 45 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 360,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 88,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 25 mg <br>Substance C: 10 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 20,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 89,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 70 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 70,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 90,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 2000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 900,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 91,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 110 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 440,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 92,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 90 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 120 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 7200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 760,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 93,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 85 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 80 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 4900 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 595,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 94,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 90 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 6400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 520,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 95,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 630,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 96,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 20 mg <br>Substance B: 95 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 30 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 97,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 90 mg <br>Substance D: 75 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 98,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 125 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 1400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 99,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 100 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 100 mg <br>Substance D: 65 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 325,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 100,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 45 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 210,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 101,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 100 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 375,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 102,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 40 mg <br>Substance D: 180 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 4000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 103,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 25 mg <br>Substance C: 85 mg <br>Substance D: 65 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 195,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 104,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 80 mg <br>Substance B: 25 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 65 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 105,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 60 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 175,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 106,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 100 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 900 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 225,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 107,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 250,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 108,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 3200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 109,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 90,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 110,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 85 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 3200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 640,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 111,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 140 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 560,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 112,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 65 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 3600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 260,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 113,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 45 mg <br>Substance D: 155 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 3500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 225,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 114,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 160 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 6300 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 675,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 115,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 45 mg <br>Substance D: 95 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 116,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 100 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 6000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1000,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 117,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 75 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 1000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 118,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 40 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 3500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 119,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 45 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 115 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 230,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 120,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 115 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 345,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 121,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 3200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 440,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 122,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 50,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 123,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 5600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 124,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 125,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 10 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 125 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 4800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 600,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 126,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 165 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 6400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 200,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 127,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 128,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 95 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 2400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 100,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 129,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 100 mg <br>Substance C: 10 mg <br>Substance D: 190 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 5400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 210,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 130,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 20 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 4500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 131,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 55 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 4200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 455,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 132,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 70 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 133,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 90 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 4000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 300,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 134,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 85 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 45 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 1500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 225,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 135,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 150 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 4500 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 136,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 10 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 450,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 137,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 175 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 7200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 720,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 138,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 160,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 139,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 170 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2700 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 165,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 140,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 160 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2700 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 180,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 141,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 45 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 90 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 7200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 80,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 142,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 5000 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 550,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 143,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 105,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 144,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 60 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 900 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 120,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 145,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 110 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 660,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 146,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 90 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 140,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 147,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 140 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 2100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 240,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 148,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 70 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 4800 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 680,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 149,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 100 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 1200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 420,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 150,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 85 mg <br>Substance D: 220 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 3600 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 880,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 151,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 115 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 60 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 11.5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 152,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 170 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 7 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1.7,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 153,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 140 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 154,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 10 mg <br>Substance D: 130 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 40 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 155,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 170 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 400 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 12.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 156,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 157,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 158,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 90 mg <br>Substance D: 70 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 150 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 35,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 159,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 100 mg <br>Substance D: 65 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 25 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 160,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 25 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 110 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 40 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 5.5,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 161,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 20 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 7,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 162,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 25 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 155 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 14 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 163,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 95 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 8 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.95,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 164,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 50 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 10 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 3.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 165,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 95 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 20 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 2 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.95,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 166,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 70 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 8 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 167,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 90 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 40 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 8 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1.2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 168,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 60 mg <br>Substance C: 90 mg <br>Substance D: 45 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 70 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 3.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 169,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 95 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 195 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 40 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 4.75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 170,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 145 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 160 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 29,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 171,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 55 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 14 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1.1,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 172,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 25 mg <br>Substance C: 70 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 8 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 173,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 60 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 125 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 16 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 174,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 20 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 45 mg <br>Substance D: 55 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 140 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 10,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 175,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 80 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 20 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 16,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 176,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 200 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 16 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1.7,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 177,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 35 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 100 mg <br>Substance D: 90 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 5 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.9,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 178,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 60 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 80 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 12,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 179,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 10 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 24 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 180,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 100 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 100 mg <br>Substance D: 185 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 40 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 181,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 100 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 2 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.95,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 182,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 95 mg <br>Substance B: 90 mg <br>Substance C: 30 mg <br>Substance D: 45 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 16 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 3.8,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 183,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 55 mg <br>Substance B: 45 mg <br>Substance C: 75 mg <br>Substance D: 65 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 20 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 3.75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 184,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 65 mg <br>Substance B: 70 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 100 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 4 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 2.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 185,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 45 mg <br>Substance B: 30 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 55 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 20 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 2.25,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 186,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 80 mg <br>Substance B: 20 mg <br>Substance C: 20 mg <br>Substance D: 105 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 28 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 4.2,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 187,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 10 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 105 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 80 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 3,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 188,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 75 mg <br>Substance C: 65 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 200 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 37.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 189,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 75 mg <br>Substance B: 15 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 75 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 4 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 190,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 70 mg <br>Substance B: 50 mg <br>Substance C: 35 mg <br>Substance D: 30 ml <br>Water to 500 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 14,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 191,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 10 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 60 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 16 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 192,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 80 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 15 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 20 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 1.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 193,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 95 mg <br>Substance D: 30 ml <br>Water to 300 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 12 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 2.6,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 194,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 100 mg <br>Substance B: 85 mg <br>Substance C: 40 mg <br>Substance D: 55 ml <br>Water to 400 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 20 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 2.75,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 195,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 15 mg <br>Substance B: 90 mg <br>Substance C: 55 mg <br>Substance D: 35 ml <br>Water to 700 ml <br>How much of substance A is required to make 35 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.75,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 196,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 20 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 15 mg <br>Substance D: 100 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 45 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 2,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 197,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 50 mg <br>Substance B: 35 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 105 ml <br>Water to 900 ml <br>How much of substance C is required to make 450 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 40,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 198,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 80 mg <br>Substance B: 10 mg <br>Substance C: 80 mg <br>Substance D: 100 ml <br>Water to 800 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 32 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 0.4,
    "Units": "mg"
  },
  {
    "Number": 199,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 40 mg <br>Substance B: 40 mg <br>Substance C: 50 mg <br>Substance D: 90 ml <br>Water to 600 ml <br>How much of substance D is required to make 60 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 9,
    "Units": "ml"
  },
  {
    "Number": 200,
    "Question": "A formula for a solution is: <br> Substance A: 30 mg <br>Substance B: 65 mg <br>Substance C: 25 mg <br>Substance D: 25 ml <br>Water to 200 ml <br>How much of substance B is required to make 100 ml of the solution?",
    "Answer": 32.5,
    "Units": "mg"
  }
]
